trendsupdates.com 2017-12-01

# Privacy | Trends Updates

TrendsUpdates.com Privacy Policy

TrendsUpdates.com is a blog for that has with time become a source of inspiration for industry professionals, savvy bloggers, dedicated readers and gluttonously nosy. Featuring elite products and news from the niche industry including Luxury, gadgets, technology, fashion, estate, auctions and emerging trends, stands TrendsUpdates welcoming your stay here.

Our aim is to assure that your hunt for hi-end yet daily-used products ends here. Infiltrate ideas and tactical advantage axle on the capability to foresee trends and discover the next big thing. And we here take pride in owning one. Each day, TrendsUpdates features a daily dose of attention grabbing products and feels good in feeding its readers’ in a fresh ambiance. Your personal privacy is EXTREMELY important to us. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect and use your personal identifying information. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully, and if you have any questions, please feel free to contact us.

By using TrendsUpdates.com, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as outlined in the Privacy Policy. From time to time, we may update the Privacy Policy and we will post a notice of significant changes on the site. You should visit this page periodically to review any such changes to the Privacy Policy.

The information we collect

When you register to become a member of TrendsUpdates.com, we collect your name, email address and optionally your hometown, state and country. Your name and email will never be shared, rented, bartered or sold with other users or third-party companies. All information entered about you will only be used by TrendsUpdates.com to display on the site and will never be shared, rented, bartered, sold or exchanged any other purposeful manner. The website, however, is accessible by anyone with an internet connection and a web browser, which means that any words and photos you post can be copied by any other internet user. That is the nature of the internet and though we discourage anyone from abusing that option, it is something that must be noted.

In order to provide the best possible service and detect and correct site errors, we collect aggregate information about use of the site (such as which page are most often viewed) and we collect information about your computer, such as such as browser type, browser language, and IP address. This information as well is never shared with anyone.

How we use your information

Your human name and email will never be shared with anyone in anyway. If you chose to enter your human hometown, state or country that information will be displayed in any of web pages on the site, and does not share any other personal information or allow access to it. Currently we use your submitted email to notify you about latest post, but the requestor never sees that email. When a user submits a Tell-A-Friend form we never store or copy any of the sender or recipient emails for any period of time.

TrendsUpdates does not claim rights for the pictures uploaded or the text information you add to the site. Please note, however, that TrendsUpdates.com is a public site and thus all photos and information you provide are available to anyone with internet access. Due to the nature of the internet, it is impossible for TrendsUpdates.com to be a protectorate of your facts and photos, so you should never post a photo or fact that you do not now or ever want someone else to have access to.

Legal requests

You understand and agree that TrendsUpdates.com may access, preserve, and disclose your personal information and the contents of your account if required to do so by law or in a good faith belief that such access preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process, such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order, or to protect the rights and property of TrendsUpdates.com, its affiliates or the public.

Controlling your personal information

You have complete control of the information you submit to TrendsUpdates. You may at anytime edit any information or remove your personal accounts entirely. TrendsUpdates.com only requires a user give a valid email while you have an account so we may contact you.

Please note, we reserve the right to transfer your submitted information in the event of a transfer of ownership of TrendsUpdates.com, such as acquisition by or merger with another company. In such an event, TrendsUpdates.com will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

Cookies

We send “cookies” to your computer and use such cookies as described here. A cookie is a piece of data that identifies you as a unique user. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service and make the service easier to use for our members. We do this by storing user preferences in cookies and by tracking user trends – for example, we use cookies to allow you to automatically log in to the service after the first user session.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Be aware, however, that some parts of TrendsUpdates.com may not function properly if you refuse cookies.

External links

TrendsUpdates.com may contain links to other web sites. These other sites maintain their own policies regarding cookies and the collection and use of personal information.

Security

We use industry standard security measures to protect your information so that it is not made available to unauthorized parties. If you have any questions regarding which measures and techniques we use, feel free to contact us.

Contacting Us

You can always contact us at any time at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Unsubscribing

You can unsubscribe at any time. If you are a member, please write a mail to unsubscribe at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) If you are not a member, but are subscribed to one of our emails, go to http://feedburner.google.com/fb/a/mailverify?uri=TrendsUpdates to unsubscribe.

Have other questions?

Again, feel free to contact us any time, and if you have further questions about [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
